Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - Probes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:05:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159803)
  - Murder Inc., 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is distorted. Audio hiss and hum can be heard. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159456)
  - Triumph of Death - The Mad, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:27:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159787)
  - Bob Savene, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159811)
  - Hitmakin' with the Hitmakers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159829)
  - Mundanes, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Metromen, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - The Machine, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Mad Oppy, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Animal Slaves, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Spines, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - The Sheiks, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Nurses, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Nolan Voydd AKA David Feldere, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Screams, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Splits, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - The Shades, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Sloth, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Paul McMahon - Adult Child, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Transformation, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Bill White Acre, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - Last Straw, 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - "Big.FRENCH", 1980 1989 (Box 119)
  - TBA, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Gift, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Mending Wall, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Hope - Take Responsibility, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Hope, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - "I.Q." - The Intensity Quotient, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - David Kelly, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Measure of Disorder, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - TBA, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - 5 songs by TBA, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Rubber Rubber, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - KatLane, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - M.P.C., 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Daina + The Tribe, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Shaking Ray Levis, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Acrylix, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Condition, 1980 1989 (Box 120)
  - Keshavan, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:33:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. An echo, at times, can be heard on the program. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902041)
  - Volts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:55:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. Static can be heard. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902058)
  - Nag Nag Nag, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902066)
  - Xenex, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There is a warble in the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902074)
  - Breakfast Club, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:29:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. Audio is unbalanced. Dropouts in the audio can be heard. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902082)
  - Pictures, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio can be heard. Static is present. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902090)
  - Various; Friends, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 01:30:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902108)
  - Stripoker, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902116)
  - Neutron Blonde, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902124)
  - Black Iris, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); An echo in the program can be heard at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902132)
  - The YardApes, 1981 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static and speed fluctuations are preesnt. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the program are present. An echo in the program is present at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902140)
  - Moscow Artist, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902157)
  - Spoil, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902165)
  - Breakfast in Bed, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902173)
  - Western Voice, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902181)
  - Corvairs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902199)
  - Syntax Error, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Audio is unbalanced. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002140902207)
  - Riff Doctors, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021593)
  - Anti-Matter, 1982; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021585)
  - The Public Servants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021577)
  - Fishman, 1984; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021569)
  - Factual, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021551)
  - Bag People, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 122, Item barcode 39002093758747)
  - Cargo Cult, 1984 (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021544)
  - Skin, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021536)
  - Taller, Sedition, Glass, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021528)
  - The Next Tape, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021510)
  - Mending Wall, 1986 March 24; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021502)
  - Red Zero, 1984; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021494)
  - Uranus, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021486)
  - Snuky, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021478)
  - Judy's Tiny Head, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021452)
  - Bop Harvey, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021460)
  - The Cult Figures, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 122, Item barcode 39002141021445)
  - Plaid, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Animal Slaves - Secret Sharer, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Neo Boys, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Blue Blue Blue, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - TBA, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Saturn Alley, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - "Victor.I.A", 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Shrug, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Das Damen - Too Hot For Hollywood, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Blitz Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Camarillo Brillo, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - The Stick Men, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Mark Oliver, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Great Plains - Born in a Barn, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Turbines, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Brilliance, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Scott Morgan, 1980 1989 (Box 123)
  - Raze, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Hizohi, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Sushi Bar Rap, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Real Politik, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Bardo, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Down Avenue, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Robert Ruttman, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Velvascurge, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Sharks, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Richard Peck Group, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Punts, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Krankhafte Phantasten, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Mitchell Bechet, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - "ibm", 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Instant Relief, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - The Wild Ones, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - WRGB and The Bongos, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - New Bra, 1980 1989 (Box 124)
  - Ramsey Najm and The Nervous System, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906414)
  - Party Tar, 1981 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:23:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906406)
  - Tim Warren, 1966; 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906398)
  - Spaces, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the program are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906380)
  - M-1 Alternative, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the program are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906372)
  - Neon Scream, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:33:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. Static is present. High amounts of buxx are present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906364)
  - Mantra Factory, 1985; 1 Audiocassette (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906356)
  - Klō, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906349)
  - No Work, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906331)
  - Red, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:57:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906323)
  - The Nothing, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140903502)
  - Tim Milk, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:58:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static and high amounts of buzz are present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906315)
  - Parkside Gents, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:36:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906307)
  - Pidgeons, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:31:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is in silence from 00:18:52-00:30:14. The program is muffled at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. There is a warble in the audio. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906299)
  - "The Oooze", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906273)
  - Mondo Condo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts are present. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906281)
  - Neva Small, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906265)
  - Peter and the Girlfriends, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:23:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 125, Item barcode 39002140906257)
  - Basket Case Baby Boom, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Silent Men, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Details at Eleven, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Sid Presley, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - "Murmor of the Heart", 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Angels in Vain, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - The Penetrators, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Razor's Edge, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - No Man, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Minors Aloud, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Panic Squad, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - The Pulse, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Religions of the World, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Punishment Park, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Saturn Alley, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Red Effect, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - New Math, 1980 1989 (Box 126)
  - Richard Lloyd - Master Tape, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Bottom Line, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Mudd Club, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - We At CBGB's, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - live, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Ritz, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Bottom Line, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - The Peppermint Lounge, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Lloyd Dance, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Ritz, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Lloyd (Backtrack), 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - Real Time, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Dean & The Weenies, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd - The Peppermint Lounge, 1980 1989 (Box 127)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Richard Lloyd - Boxing Day, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, Roughs, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls - mix, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls - Texas Tavern, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls - remixes, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls - mixes, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls - remixes, 1980 1989 (Box 128)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls - demo, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls - final mix, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls - All songs & arrangements, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Two Nice Girls, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Spiral Jetty, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - The Del-Lords, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Book of Love, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Heal The Nation, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Blue Angel, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Cruisin', 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Elixir, Neil Davidson, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Wammo, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Hi-Techs, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Rufty Tufty, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Renegade, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - Paramour, 1980 1989 (Box 129)
  - No Sisters, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968331)
  - The Method Actors, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. High amounts of buzz are present. Dropouts in the audio are present at about 00:09:45. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968323)
  - The Judy's, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:51:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled and dropouts in the audio can be heard. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Audio has an echo to it at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968315)
  - Dominatrix, 1983 December 2; 1 Audiocassette; 00:44:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968349)
  - Jim F. The Dark, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio dropouts are in the program. Static is present. An echo in the audio can be heard at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968356)
  - They Might Be Giants, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140967002)
  - Mickey Clean, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968364)
  - Nina Canal, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968372)
  - Martha and the Muffins, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:58:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968380)
  - Controlled Bleeding, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. There is a warble in the program. The program can be heard in the right channel only for about 11 seconds at about 00:31:08. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968398)
  - Robert Hazard and the Heroes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968406)
  - The Hipnotics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:02:22-00:02:42. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. There is a warble in the audio. The program is in silence from 00:09:11-00:09:37. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968414)
  - Riff Doctors, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968422)
  - The Gift, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968430)
  - Band of Outsiders, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:59:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. Left channel audio dropouts out around 00:05:56-00:40:53. Crosstalk is present around 00:40:53. Static is present. Volume fluctuations are present in the left channel. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968448)
  - Breathing - Snarling, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:01:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968455)
  - Anti-Matter, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968463)
  - The Vipers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968471)
  - Limbo District, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968489)
  - Swans, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:51:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968497)
    Entire second half/side is unrelated talk radio.
  - Tirez Tirez, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:24:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 130, Item barcode 39002140968505)
  - The Immigrant Rock, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - The Western Voice, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - The R&B Cadets, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Raybeats, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Sarah Flynn, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Razormusics, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - The Undead, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Associates, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - La Peste, Chuck Braverman, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Chris Roman D.J., 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Kit Hain, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Limbo Race, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - The Undead, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Saucers, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - (ILLEGIBLE), 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Love Don't Need a Reason, The Healing Power of Love, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Tirez Tirez, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - The President of the United States, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Personal Effects, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Mofungo, 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - (UNLABELED), 1980 1989 (Box 131)
  - Steve Pichett, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - DJ Kathleen Abrams, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - Timetwins Dare, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - Therapy Hurley - F.L.O, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - Chelsea Funk Orchestra, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - Cha-Cha Fernandez & The Slumlords, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - R. Mutt, 1980 1989 (Box 132)
  - Lou Miami and the Kozmetix, undated; 1 Audiotape Reel; 00:04:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); An echo, at times, can be heard on the program. Speed fluctuations are present. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908006)
  - Max Navarre, "Nowhere to Run", 1980 March 12; 1 Audiotape Reel 1/4" tape, 5-inch reel; 00:02:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908014)
  - Max Navarre, Demo (The Max Navarre Band), 1982 June 29; 1 Audiotape Reel 1/4" tape; 5" reel; 00:08:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908022)
  - Michael Pablo Dugan, Tape for Danceteria, 1980 1989; 1 Audiotape Reel 7" reel; 00:31:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908030)
  - Hot Lunch recording, 1977 July 5; 1 Audiotape Reel 1/4 inch; diameter 7"; 01:21:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program was recorded at a very high level. High amounts of buzz can be heard. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is heavily distorted at times. The right channel was recorded at a very low level from 00:04:45-00:07:29. Speed fluctuations are present. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140904476)
  - Hot Lunch, Max's, Set I, undated; 1 Audiotape Reel 7" reel; 00:41:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. High amounts of buzz are present. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908048)
  - [Unlabeled], Hot Lunch, Max's Set II, undated; 1 Audiotape Reel 7" reel; 00:43:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002140908055)
- Video recordings of band performances, 1979 1987; Series V; 10.83 Linear Feet; (10 boxes); 131 Videocassettes; 131 video recordings on varying video cassette formats.
  This series consists of video recordings of live band performances, mostly recorded at the New York nightclub Danceteria. Performers include Richard Lloyd, Mission of Burma, Liquid Liquid, Sonic Youth, Pylon, ESG, and others. Also includes some video recordings related to the AIDS epidemic.
  - DNA, 1980 1989; 1 Videocassette (U-matic); 00:41:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Video levels are low due to lighting. (Box 133, Item barcode 39002137218260)
  - Art (The Band), 1980 1989 (Box 133)
  - Flipper, 1982 (Box 133)